(Raj:)Okay, okay.
(Raj:)Although many older women
lead vibrant, active...
I said well past it!
(Sheldon:)Excuse me,
Officer Hernandez?
(Sheldon:)Any leads on the person
who stole my belongings?
(Hernandez:)Not yet.
(Sheldon:)Well, perhaps I can help.
(Sheldon:)Sherlock Holmes
always says
(Sheldon:)when you eliminate
the impossible,
(Sheldon:)whatever remains,
however improbable,
(Sheldon:)must be the truth.
Now, have-have you
tried doing that?
(Penny:)Nope.
(Sheldon:)Well, maybe you should.
Th-Th-There's lots of books
called "Sherlock Holmes"
(Sheldon:)and there's no books
called "Officer Hernandez."
(Leonard:)Thanks again
for coming.
(Leonard:)Six hours was gonna be
a long drive by myself.
(Amy:)My pleasure.
(Amy:)And I'm not angry at all
that my boyfriend
(Amy:)was in trouble
and called you instead of me.
I love that!